{
    "id": "e8edca2def7f42968a6d922b7ba7d214",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to know …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what are you doing there",
                "what you are doing there"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e19eeb3768c846a2b9f6a42ad42f105f"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he had asked me ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I will help him",
                "I would help him",
                "I would have helped him"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6668e7a492034b46afedcabfa2a95f69"
        },
        {
            "question": "She would have come .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if you invite her",
                "if you invited her",
                "if you had invited her"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4975ef36916465cb5b305a12ee5892e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are looking forward to ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see you",
                "seeing you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d1e471c01cdf40778c2015ebfd202fa5"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner did the teacher enter the class ..................... .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when the students stopped talking",
                "than the students stopped talking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "44aef5fc532048a1a837fbd1c6e08571"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind .....................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to move a bit",
                "moving a bit"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "37d41a67a7ae41538732b6327b1924ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "Unless you study well, …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you will pass",
                "you will not pass"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75ec3ba73fe5477988b04c5f679fca57"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked ………………… that his health broke down.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very hard",
                "too hard",
                "so hard"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4614e4f06bca466fb3f2ff6e98978e2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very fond …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with her grandchildren",
                "of her grandchildren",
                "to her grandchildren"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6c56d97f0d0488da7fef7e4b489423b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very proud ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with her achievements",
                "about her achievements",
                "of her achievements"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cb97fbfa007546e59b50af2f7f7d068c"
        }
    ]
}